myskillstutor.com 2005-12-10

# Privacy Statement

**Right to Privacy**

> Achievement Technologies, Inc. and the companies we represent respect your rights to privacy when using our websites. We understand the need for Internet security and the privacy protection requirements of schools. Accordingly, we adhere to the following privacy policies where relevant to the websites: 

**Notice**

> We will inform you when we need information that identifies you or allows us to contact you. We do not collect personal information such as social security numbers, personal addresses, or personal demographic information. We do collect information about your school, its address, and your preferred email address. In general this information is required before viewing premium portions of this site, such as sample lessons, or signing up for newsletters and other special offers. We will use this information to: 
> 
>   * Correctly identify you and your school in our database 
>   * Contact you regarding your interest in our products & services 
>   * Inform you of special offers, upgrades to our service and related information which may be of interest to you 
> 

**Registration**

> In order to view certain premium portions of the site, including sample lessons, we ask you to complete a registration form. In the registration form we request contact information (including your name, school name and email address). This information is used to identify your school and to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest. It is optional for you to provide your mailing address, telephone or other contact information, but we encourage you to do so. 

**Information collection & use**

> Achievement Technologies, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Cookies**

> A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information related to their use of a particular site. When you register on the Achievement Technologies, Inc. site, we will place a cookie on your hard disk. This cookie contains no personal information. It is simply a marker that indicates that you have already registered. In this way, you will not have to re-register on each visit. Your browser may be set to reject cookies. If so, you may still use our site; however, re-registration will be required for each visit to a premium area of the site. 

**About Flash**

> ALL SkillsTutor flash files are created in-house and maintained on a highly secure server. SkillsTutor flash downloads are completely safe and do not modify user computer files in any way. 

**Log Files**

> We use IP addresses to count visitors to our site and to the pages on our site. We do not link IP addresses to personal information. 

**Ability to opt out**

> You have the right to withhold personal information by not filling out the registration form. You will still be able to use most areas of the site. We may use information obtained from you to contact you about products and services in which you might be interested. If you do not wish your information to be used in this way, you may contact us by email at [privacy@achievementtech.com](mailto:privacy@achievementtech.com) and request that your name be withheld from further contact. 

**Protecting your data**

> We take all reasonable precautions to protect your data from unauthorized use. This includes restrictions on sharing data with third parties and restrictions on access within Achievement Technologies, Inc. based on job responsibilities. 

**Enforcement**

> If you believe Achievement Technologies, Inc. has failed to adhere to these policies, please contact us at [privacy@achievementtech.com](mailto:privacy@achievementtech.com)

**Corrections**

> You may correct inaccuracies in your personal information (name, email, phone, mail, etc.), and preferences for receiving further marketing information from us by emailing us at [privacy@achievementtech.com](mailto:privacy@achievementtech.com)

**Links**

> This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Achievement Technologies, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our web site. 

**Surveys & contests**

> From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and our other products and services. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)**

> Achievement Technologies, Inc. has designed a K-8 Learning MileStones program to be appropriate for children and young students in its entirety, including its subject matter, age-specific content and language, visual and audio content, animated characters and program features. 
> 
> We recognize the importance of protecting children's online privacy and safety. 
> 
> We understand that we are prohibited by law from requiring children to disclose any additional information, than is reasonably required, in use of our products or services. 
> 
> The only personal information we collect from children is their names (first and/or last) when supplied to us by teachers or school administrators as part of the registration process. Otherwise, we do not collect personal information from children, directly, indirectly, actively or passively (such as through the use of cookies). 
> 
> Personal information is collected strictly for the purpose of tracking and reporting students' progress to authorized teachers, school administrators and/or other educational institutions. All data collected is kept strictly confidential and resides on secure web-hosting servers. Only necessary company personnel have access to this data. 
> 
> We do not use personal information to advertise, market, or sell products or services to children. 
> 
> We will not disclose children's personal information to any third party, except to the children's parents or legal guardians (provided we have express written verification from the school principal or identified administrator or purchaser of our programs, or as part of the sale or merger of our company to or with another company. 
> 
> If you would like further information or have comments or questions regarding our privacy statement, please contact: 
>
>> Achievement Technologies, Inc.  
>  10400 Little Patuxent Parkway, Suite 310  
>  Columbia, MD 21044  
>  Attention: Privacy Officer 
>> 
>> Telephone: 410-992-4800  
>  Email: [privacy@achievementtech.com](mailto:privacy@achievementtech.com)

**Notification of changes**

> If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
